{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Garage Door Repair Services","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40064/":{"taskOID":40064,"originalTaskOID":40064,"setID":387,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5048,"questionDisplayText":"Repair Needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What problem do you need repaired? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1816,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Damaged sections","answerDisplayText":"Damaged sections","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1132,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Broken springs (door will not go up)","answerDisplayText":"Broken springs (door will not go up)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7122,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Worn out hardware (side hinges)","answerDisplayText":"Worn out hardware (side hinges)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5386,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Rollers out of tracks","answerDisplayText":"Rollers out of tracks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1225,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cable off the drums","answerDisplayText":"Cable off the drums","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2006,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Door damaged, broken, dented, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Door damaged, broken, dented, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2029,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Door won't open","answerDisplayText":"Door won't open","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2028,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Door won't close","answerDisplayText":"Door won't close","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1123,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Broken door parts","answerDisplayText":"Broken door parts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2715,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Gaps around door (bottom, side or top) when closed","answerDisplayText":"Gaps around door (bottom, side or top) when closed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1024,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Bent or damaged tracks","answerDisplayText":"Bent or damaged tracks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5079,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Garage Door","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of door needs to be repaired?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5535,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sectional roll up","answerDisplayText":"Sectional roll up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4377,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"One piece tilt up","answerDisplayText":"One piece tilt up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5047,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Garage Door","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Of what material  is your damaged garage door made?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6696,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1751,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Custom (wood application)","answerDisplayText":"Custom (wood application)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2427,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5048,"questionDisplayText":"Repair Needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What problem do you need repaired? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1816,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Damaged sections","answerDisplayText":"Damaged sections","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1132,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Broken springs (door will not go up)","answerDisplayText":"Broken springs (door will not go up)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7122,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Worn out hardware (side hinges)","answerDisplayText":"Worn out hardware (side hinges)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5386,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Rollers out of tracks","answerDisplayText":"Rollers out of tracks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1225,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cable off the drums","answerDisplayText":"Cable off the drums","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2006,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Door damaged, broken, dented, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Door damaged, broken, dented, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2029,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Door won't open","answerDisplayText":"Door won't open","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2028,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Door won't close","answerDisplayText":"Door won't close","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1123,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Broken door parts","answerDisplayText":"Broken door parts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2715,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Gaps around door (bottom, side or top) when closed","answerDisplayText":"Gaps around door (bottom, side or top) when closed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1024,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Bent or damaged tracks","answerDisplayText":"Bent or damaged tracks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1816,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Damaged sections","answerDisplayText":"Damaged sections","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1132,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Broken springs (door will not go up)","answerDisplayText":"Broken springs (door will not go up)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7122,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Worn out hardware (side hinges)","answerDisplayText":"Worn out hardware (side hinges)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5386,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Rollers out of tracks","answerDisplayText":"Rollers out of tracks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1225,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cable off the drums","answerDisplayText":"Cable off the drums","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2006,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Door damaged, broken, dented, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Door damaged, broken, dented, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2029,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Door won't open","answerDisplayText":"Door won't open","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2028,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Door won't close","answerDisplayText":"Door won't close","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1123,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Broken door parts","answerDisplayText":"Broken door parts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2715,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Gaps around door (bottom, side or top) when closed","answerDisplayText":"Gaps around door (bottom, side or top) when closed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1024,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Bent or damaged tracks","answerDisplayText":"Bent or damaged tracks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5079,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Garage Door","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of door needs to be repaired?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5535,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sectional roll up","answerDisplayText":"Sectional roll up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4377,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"One piece tilt up","answerDisplayText":"One piece tilt up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5535,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sectional roll up","answerDisplayText":"Sectional roll up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4377,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"One piece tilt up","answerDisplayText":"One piece tilt up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5047,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Garage Door","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Of what material  is your damaged garage door made?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6696,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1751,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Custom (wood application)","answerDisplayText":"Custom (wood application)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2427,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6696,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1751,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Custom (wood application)","answerDisplayText":"Custom (wood application)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2427,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40064/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40064,"taskName":"Garage Door - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair a Garage Door","xmTaskDescriptor":"Garage Door Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":98,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Garage Door automatic wood vinyl","textMessagingName":"Repr Garage Door","rolloverLongDesc":"Note separate category for automatic openers","rolloverShortDesc":"Repair or replace panels, tracks or mechanisms.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair a Garage Door.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"\u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e Garage Door Repair | Garage Opener Repairs","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":36,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Garage Door Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Garage Door - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Garage Door Repair Project","urlName":"Garage-Door-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Garage Door Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"Garage,Door,automatic,wood,vinyl,steel,roll,overhead,,glass,fiberglass,tracks","emcCategoryOid":-12036,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":387,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}